yippy.com 2018-12-16

# Yippy.com - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Commitment

Yippy, Inc. ("Yippy or We ") is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of the users of our services. The following describes the information collection and use practices for the services offered on Yippy.com ("Yippy") and other properties.

### Data Collection (Absence of Personally Identifiable Information)

No personally identifiable information is ever required by Yippy. This means Yippy never seeks any information related to your name, telephone number, address, or even your email address unless you request a Yippy Service where that information is required. Yippy is intended to be an anonymous service. We do collect limited non-personally identifying information that your browser makes available, which is not saved after session ends. This log information may include your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referral data, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies (described below) that may uniquely identify your browser while in a session. Yippy will not track anyone for any reason, unless such information is required to comply with court orders or subpoenas or when required to do so by law, which as of 2018 has never occurred in our 9 year history.  Yippy protects your privacy, and always has since inception.

### Cookies

We do not use cookies to uniquely identify you or to track your behavior. A “cookie” is a packet of information sent by a server to a Web browser and then sent back by the browser each time it accesses that server, or to cache user preferences (such as but not limited to user selected graphics). We use cookies only to store personalized settings (such as but not limited to display options and adult filter) and to optimize the speed of Yippy for search by caching your results in a session. By default most browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies; and still be able to make searches on Yippy.

### Use of Collected Information

Yippy does not sell or provide personally identifiable information to any third parties. Yippy provides no advertising in our search, or third party tracking scripts.

### Links

The privacy policy of sites displayed as search results, or otherwise linked to by Yippy, is not controlled by Yippy. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.

### Policy Changes

Yippy constantly strives to provide the best service. As new products and changes to existing products are made, Yippy reserves the right to amend this Yippy Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the current information collection and usage practices associated with your use of Yippy. Your use of Yippy is also governed by the Terms of Service.

### More Information

If you have any comments or questions about your privacy, please contact [info@yippyinc.com](mailto:info@yippyinc.com)

### Copyright and Trademark

All contents of this Web site are: Copyright (c) 2018 Yippy, Inc. All rights reserved.

The Yippy and associated Marks that appear throughout Yippy belong to Yippy, Inc. and are protected by trademark laws. To seek permission to use any of the Yippy Marks, please contact us at [info@yippyinc.com](mailto:info@yippyinc.com)
